So our first exercise will be something similar to what we did in the previous lesson but a bit different
所以我们的第一个练习将与我们在上一课中所做的类似，但有点不同
because this is a full variation.
因为这是一个完整的变体。
We looked before it how we could say things a little bit differently and also reduce the redundancy
我们在它之前查看了我们如何能够以不同的方式说事情并减少冗余
and any repetition that we could cut out to make it simpler.
以及我们可以删除以使其更简单的任何重复。
Well we can do the same thing but just go for a full variation.
好吧，我们可以做同样的事情，但只需要一个完整的变化。
In other words we can take some creative liberties we can do what we want but it has to stay in the
换句话说，我们可以采取一些创造性的自由，我们可以做我们想做的事，但它必须留在
general area and the events pretty much have to be the same although maybe we can do it from a different
一般区域和事件几乎必须相同，尽管也许我们可以从不同的地方做到这一点
a different perspective.
不同的视角。
But basically what we're going to do is rewrite the whole thing and you can do this with a maybe two
但基本上我们要做的是重写整个事情，你可以用大约两个
paragraphs from a book that you're reading.
您正在阅读的书中的段落。
You might try to do it with a big paragraph from an article that you're reading.
您可能会尝试使用您正在阅读的文章中的一大段来做到这一点。
Whatever as long as it's something that's long enough and has enough detail so that you can really explore
随便，只要它足够长，有足够的细节，这样你就可以真正探索
it and do a really good variation or rephrase it can also say that we're rephrasing it and now we're
它并做一个非常好的变化或改写它也可以说我们正在改写它，现在我们
going to look at a short story very short story and see if we can rephrase it.
打算看一个短篇小说，看看我们是否可以改写它。
So let's just read through this.
所以让我们通读一遍。
Something unusual happened as Alex made his way home from class.
亚历克斯下课回家时发生了一些不寻常的事情。
He had been walking through campus when suddenly a stranger wearing a black mask holding a small knife
他正走在校园里，突然一个戴着黑色面具的陌生人拿着小刀
stepped out from behind a tree and demanded that Alex hand over his wallet.
从树后走出来，要求亚历克斯交出他的钱包。
Of course Alex valued his life more than his money and it seemed like the mugger meant business.
当然，亚历克斯更看重他的生命而不是他的钱，而且抢劫犯似乎是认真的。
But as he was taking out his wallet the stranger lowered the knife and said You're a coward before running
但是当他拿出钱包的时候，陌生人放下了刀，说你是个胆小鬼，然后跑了
away into the darkness.
远离黑暗。
OK now I think you can probably get the idea.
好的，现在我想你可能明白了。
The meaning of that story wallet is where you keep your money.
那个故事钱包的意义是你存放钱的地方。
The mugger is the person who may steal your money on the street.
抢劫犯是可能在街上偷你钱的人。
They'll say Hey give me your wallet.
他们会说嘿把你的钱包给我。
That is a mugger and to mean business means that you're not joking around.
那是个抢劫犯，意思是生意意味着你不是在开玩笑。
It's serious.
很严重。
You really intend to.
你真的打算。
If you don't give me your wallet I will stab you with this knife.
如果你不给我你的钱包，我会用这把刀刺伤你。
All right.
好的。
Now I've written a variation of this.
现在我写了一个变体。
I've basically taken this story which I also wrote and I wrote it again in a different way.
我基本上把这个故事也写了一遍，然后用不同的方式再写了一遍。
And I've written it from the perspective of the mugger.
我是从抢劫犯的角度写的。
So that is a creative liberty that I have taken.
所以这是我采取的创造性自由。
So what you can do is try to write it from different perspectives in different ways and really explore
所以你能做的就是试着从不同的角度用不同的方式去写，真正去探索
the event.
事件。
It's a very good creative exercise.
这是一个非常好的创意练习。
OK.
好的。
Now let's look at my variation of this.
现在让我们看看我对此的变化。
And notice that it's from the perspective of Alex's friend who I've decided is the one who was mugging
请注意，从亚历克斯朋友的角度来看，我认为他是抢劫的人
Alex.
亚历克斯。
It was fake.
那是假的。
He was just playing a joke on his friend his roommate.
他只是在和他的室友朋友开个玩笑。
He wanted to scare him.
他想吓唬他。
That's why he said You're a coward.
所以他说你是个懦夫。
In my mind OK so I'm writing it from his perspective Alex's roommate played a horrible prank on him
在我看来，好吧，所以我是从他的角度来写的，亚历克斯的室友对他开了一个可怕的恶作剧
last night.
昨夜。
He put on a ski mask and hid behind a tree until dark.
他戴上滑雪面罩，躲在一棵树后面直到天黑。
Then when he spotted Alex walking back to the dorm he jumped out.
然后，当他看到亚历克斯走回宿舍时，他跳了出来。
He realized he might be taking things a little far with the pocket knife in his hand.
他意识到他手中的小刀可能会把事情做得有点过分。
But Alex is petrified face made it all worthwhile just to see what would happen.
但亚历克斯被石化的脸让这一切都值得只是看看会发生什么。
He demanded Alex's wallet feeling the joke had gone far enough.
他要求亚历克斯的钱包觉得这个玩笑已经够远了。
He said You're a coward before disappearing into the shadows.
他说你是个懦夫，然后消失在阴影中。
He laughed all the way back to the dorm.
一路笑着回宿舍。
OK.
好的。
So basically it's the same story two different perspectives.
所以基本上这是同一个故事两个不同的观点。
You get the idea.
你明白了。
The point is exploring within the constraints or the limits of the original story and the events that
重点是在原始故事和事件的约束或限制内探索
happen so keep the events the same.
发生所以保持事件相同。
Keep the basic story the same.
保持基本故事不变。
Explore what's possible within that play with the language tell a couple of versions of it doesn't have
探索这门语言在游戏中的可能性，告诉它的几个版本没有
to be from another perspective but it's a great exercise if you want to be a better writer and it's
从另一个角度来看，但如果你想成为一个更好的作家，这是一个很好的练习，而且
a great exercise to help you think in English a little bit differently and develop your basic habits
一个很好的练习，可以帮助您以不同的方式思考英语并培养您的基本习惯
and and your skills in how you put sentences together.
以及你如何将句子组合在一起的技能。
So you practice this a lot.
所以你经常练习这个。
You're going to get really good at that and you're gonna become a much better writer as well because
你会变得非常擅长，你也会成为一个更好的作家，因为
each version should be better than the last.
每个版本都应该比上一个更好。
And then you can go back and look at it and see how can I improve.
然后你可以回去看看它，看看我该如何改进。
OK.
好的。
So that is the sentence variation or the rephrasing exercise.
这就是句子变化或改写练习。
Now let's go on and do another one which is also really really useful.
现在让我们继续做另一个也非常有用的。